{
    "subject": "resource/Dave_Carter_and_Tracy_Grammer",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Dave Carter and Tracy Grammer are from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9576608538627625,
            "question": "Can we say that Dave Carter and Tracy Grammer are American artists?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9408755898475647,
            "question": "Where are Dave Carter and Tracy Grammer from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9392459988594055,
            "question": "Is Tracy Grammer also from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9169594049453735,
            "question": "Are Dave Carter and Tracy Grammer American musicians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7842299342155457,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Dave Carter and Tracy Grammer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7734822630882263,
            "question": "Do both Dave Carter and Tracy Grammer hail from the same place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7327883839607239,
            "question": "Where might we find more information about Dave Carter and Tracy Grammer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6018111109733582,
            "question": "What country is Dave Carter originally from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4344457685947418,
            "question": "Do you know anything about Dave Carter and Tracy Grammer's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2302590310573578,
            "question": "Besides being from the United States, what else is known about them?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dave Carter and Tracy Grammer are from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8927_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know anything about Dave Carter and Tracy Grammer's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8927_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Dave Carter originally from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8927_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might we find more information about Dave Carter and Tracy Grammer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8927_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8927_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8927_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8927_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8927_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8927_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8927_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8927_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8927_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8927_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8927_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information mentions that Tracy Grammer is an American folk singer, which implies that she and her partner Dave Carter are from the United States. Therefore, the statement \"Dave Carter and Tracy Grammer are from the United States\" is supported by the provided documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}